tan
me
Sickness will get better, don't worry
I'm going to be healthy
Wait a minute.
Beautiful.
Shall we begin?
Let's do it.
It's loose.
We don't like to say this ourselves, but...
Unlucky.
Unlucky girl.
So you're an unlucky girl.
I've been writing about a recent episode of bad luck.
Which one do you want to start with?
Go ahead.
Atachi?
Atachi.
A little bit.
It's a rather expensive hair dryer I got as a Christmas present for myself.
I've always wanted one.
I bought it for myself as a present.
But when I pushed it, it stopped blowing air.
It just went silent.
How many times did you use it?
About a month.
That's very short.
I was really shocked for a month or two.
I haven't had any luck.I'm not lucky, but...
You know when you're not having a good day.
There's a zone, right?
Yeah, there's a zone, and I thought I was in that zone, but for starters, there's the first one, and then the second one, and then the third one.
That's the second one.
It's still there, isn't it?
The TV suddenly stops working.
Scary, right?
No matter how hard you try, there's always something to stick in the back.
I tried everything, but still no sound.
And the wind won't blow.
That's right.
No sound.
It's going to the electrics.
Go ahead.
When you're shooting a live photo or a game app, the camera doesn't shut off first.
And the next time you get a shot, there's always a monitor right next to it that shows the picture that was taken.
Now it's all black and it doesn't show up.
Scary!
I think I'm an electrician.
You're transmitting.
Yeah, I think electric people are covered in electricity.
Like the Avengers.
Oh, cool!
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
It's a positive thing, isn't it?
Yes, and then he stops the cab meter, too.
I guess I'm a little lucky.
I'm really sorry, but... Maybe I'm lucky, but I'm really, really sorry.
I don't usually stop the meter on the way to the airport, so the driver doesn't even see it, because the meter is running.
So when we arrived at the destination, it was like, "Oh, that's not right.
So I was able to take a little more time off than usual.
I guess I got a little lucky, but it's scary.
It's too scary this time of year!
And last but not least...
I've been sick all summer.
Oh, yes, there was a time, wasn't there?
I wanted to participate in Tokyo Idol Festival, but I couldn't this year.
It's so boring in the summer time, isn't it?
I've been sick all the time, and this was the worst.
It was a long time, wasn't it?
Well then, let's have Haruharu's!
The moment I left the restaurant, a bird droppings fell on my shoulder.
Your shoulder? Bird poop is pretty lucky.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Good luck.
Like that.
It's good luck.
It's lucky.
I thought I was lucky. I thought I was lucky.
But then it started to sink in.
I didn't like it.
Why didn't you take it right away?
I just wanted to see it.
You don't have this kind of experience, do you?
But I have.
When I was a little girl, it fell on my head like a ton of bricks.That thing fell on my head like crazy when I was a little kid.
I could hear the bike voice.
I was like "ah!
I thought it was a lucky break for me.
And then I was making mud dumplings in the park when I was a kid, and they fell out.
That's amazing.
It's really great, isn't it?
I was used to that.
I was used to it.
You missed the 4th Hinatan Festival because you injured your knee walking and bumped into someone.
Recently... this year...
Recently.
And before that, didn't you have a flesh separation?
That's right.
I'm in the foot zone at this time.
I'm in the foot zone.
Foot zone
I was in the foot zone.
Here's the foot zone.
Here, here, here, here.
Foot zone.
We're going to have to go up.
Let's get you out of here.
Are you better now?
Yes, I'm much better.
That's great. That was really scary.
Yes, I'm fine. Yes, it's okay.
Good.
Next...
I went back to my parents' house when I joined the Happy Trine Tour 2023 in Nagoya Park.
Yeah, yeah...
The water heater was broken, so I couldn't warm myself in the water bath.
Icing!
I was icing my whole body.
Icing before bed is tough.
Last one.
What the hell?
Every time I put on my beige pants, it rains, so I look like a person who's been rained on more than anyone else.
Oh.
Beige makes you darker.
Yes, I've been hit so hard that I wonder where I've been...
Aaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaah!
In this case, we have no choice but to go up!
Yes, I'm going up!
I'm going up today!
Up!
Okay, I'm going on tour.
Let's go!
First day of the tour.
I look like a dokiri. What am I going to do? What's that noise?
We've arrived at the shrine of celebration. Thank you very much.
A white shrine gate. I'm so happy we're finally here.
I'm already happy. Excited. I'm already happy.
I'm going through the gate.
Excuse me. Excuse me.
All right.
It's kind of mysterious, isn't it? The air.
Yes, it's refreshing.
It's refreshing.
The air is clean.
I'm so happy! I haven't been able to come here much lately.
Shrines and temples.
I'm so happy!
This is one of the most powerful spots in Japan.
That's right.
Yes, yes, yes.
Wait, he really wanted to come here, didn't he?
Yes, I did.
Personally.
Isn't this... Sanbon-sugi? Famous.
Yes, Sanbonsugi.
This one, I heard it's about 50 meters high.
Wow!
You don't know how long 50 meters is.
50 meters.
You can run 50 meters.
How fast can you run 50 meters? Far, far, far.
About 9.2 seconds.
Then, Haruharu can climb in 9.2 seconds.
What does it say?
500 meters.
There's an M here. There's an M in here.
There's an M in front of the plane here.
500 meters.
Next.
Shh.
Mmm.
I inhaled.
Oh, my God. My lungs are happy.
That's great.
Excuse me.
That's great. It's cool and all.
There's coolness in here.
Gosei.
We're at a new place again.
"Five lives on a wheel.
Turn the wheel up, and your wish for this life will come true. Turn it down, and your wish for the next life will come true.
This life.
I'd love to do it!
Up, up
I wish you a happy life!
It spun so beautifully.
I'd like to live in this world, too.
Yes, you are.
You said your wish will come true.
I'll make a wish.
Please, please, please.
Good morning.
Good morning
Good morningI look forward to working with you.
Something exciting.
It's an excitement zone.
I'm not in the right frame of mind.
Yes, sir.
We're ready to serve you, sir.
I'm sorry, but you'll have to serve yourself.
We do not ask you to purify yourself.
Yes, sir.
May I see that?
I'll go this way.
I'd like you both to look at them.
You can take it home.
We'll purify the whole body.
Yes, ma'am.
We can do this next time.
Yes.
This one, too.
Yes, sir.
Only this miso powder is poured.
And finally, this rice.
Oh!
That's all.
Thank you very much.
Finally, the rice is poured
Let the rice flow
Yes, sir
Thank youThank you.
Water here.
Oh!
That's great.
You made it.
He's here. He's so cool.
Here they come!
The mythological shrine of Mt. Cheongdae.
Yes, sir.
Amazing.
Good night.
Good night. - Good night.
And now...
I stand before you, Ookami of Oiwa Shrine.
To the end of the fire cloud that protects us from medicines
I will perform the festival with love and respect.
We pray
I pray.
Please proceed with the two of you to the front of the shrine building.
After you have proceeded
Please hold up the tamagushi (sacred skewer) in your hands
Please stop your prayers there.
Dokdo is over.
It started with a big drum
I was so excited
But my heart is filled with excitement.
I don't know what it isI don't know.
I feel so relaxed.
What did you ask for? A wish.
What did you ask for?
I'm working on the new mountain gate right now.
There are two parks left.
8 parks so far.
Excuse me.
Hachikouen so far
I haven't been able to do all the songs.
I've got a knee injury, right?
Yeah, I know.
That's my regret right now.
And I really want to perform all the songs in NIKKOEN.
We've all worked so hard.
I'm really rooting for you.
Thank you very much.
From the bottom of my heart
I have a fortune for you.
A fortune
I don't know how much a fortune is, but it's 100 yen.
Wait, there are a lot of them!
A fortune for the month of March
Omikuji of the day
This is a simple fortune
I wonder who's good
I'll make it a simple omikuji
I see
Hey... Hey.
Maybe this is it.
I got this.
I've been called
I've been called.
Okay.
This way
"Great Luck" (in Japanese)
Middle lucky
We did it!
That's great!
You're going to be fine.
I'm going to be healthy.
I'll be healthy.
No more stumbling
I'm sick too
If I put my prayers in, I'll be cured.
But it's just a table
It's all a stand
I lose things.
I lose things all the time.
It's hard to get out.
Give it up
Look for the red seal.
You're right... you're right.
I was going to bring my red seal book today.
I was looking for it all last night.
I couldn't find it.Because it didn't come up.
You're right.
That's great.
It's like fortune-telling.
Like fortune-telling.
There's so many.
There are a lot of them.
Oh!
This one...
This is good.
It's too bad.
I'll take this one
good luck charm
I'll take this one too.
Ta-da!
I got it!
Here's the good luck charm I got!
I'm off to the next power spot!
I'm off!
Yoo-hoo!
We're on the move!
We're at Fukuroda Falls.
We're here!
We came to see it.
Yay!
It's like a power spot!
I'd like to go to the waterfall to get some power too.
Yes, sir!
I got it!
Wow, it looks so good!Wow, looks so good!
Smells good.
Smells so good
Ayu
It's good, it's good
I want to eat it
I want some!
What's a sweet potato skewer?
Taro skewers! Here!
What's a taro skewer?
Well, I'll have one dumpling and one taro skewer, please.
A sweet potato and a dumpling, one day.
Yes, one day, please.
Thank you very much.
Yes, thank you. Bon appétit.
Thank you very much. Bon appétit.
A sweet potato skewer.
Hardly.
It's so round.
So cute!
A secret technique.
It's amazing. It's like magic.
It's like magic.
What do you think?
Taro.
Delicious.
The sauce is sweet and tangy.
It's nostalgic.
You've had it before?
I haven't.I don't have any.
I'll take the dumplings.
They are big, aren't they?
Yes, sir.
Delicious.
Want to eat?
They're very chewy. It's a soy sauce like a Mitarashi dumpling, but it's really tasty.
Oh. Mochi mochi mochi.
Mochi mochi mochi.
It's been a while since we went out to eat like this. Do you usually do it? Usually.
I don't.
Of course you don't.
I'm happy.
You're happy. It's a white tree.
Excuse me.
I'll show you the way to the waterfall.
Wow!
We're still at the entrance,
Goooood!
Here's the waterfall.
Wait, one, two, three, four.
Four tiers of waterfalls.
Here we go.
Look, it's glowing.
Daigo light.
Tunnel of light, Daigo Light
It looks like an illumination.
Yellow
Oh, it's a slope!
Eh, wait a minute. Oh, wait a minute.
Suddenly?
What is this place?
Six degrees.
Oh, my God.
That's amazing.
What?
It's beautiful.
It's a power spot.
Oh, my God.
I'll take it.
It's amazing.
Isn't it amazing?
It's amazing!
That's impressive.
Wow.
Well, I heard there's a place where you can see it from up there.
Let's go.
We're almost to the top!
Hey, hey, hey, hey, Haruharu, lucky hearts, lucky hearts.
The lucky heart
It's in the waterfall.
It looks like it's right here.
Look at this wilderness
I think I know where the heart is.
Where's the heart?Where is it, Heart?
That's amazing.
It would be dangerous if you dropped it
It's one of these.
Let's see if there's one.
I wonder if there's a heart.
Not that one... that one... that's definitely trash.
That's it.
Now where's the heart, ladies and gentlemen?
Dendendendendendendendendendendendendendendendendendendendendendendendend...
Maybe this one.
I'll do my best.
I hope that Hinata-chu will become a more beloved group.
Please, please
Please do your best
I'll do my best
I've already received a great exorcism.
We've come to a power spot like this.
We are the strongest.
We are the best.
All that bad luck I mentioned at the beginning...
We're going to get rid of it all.
It's the recklessness I've missed.
All right, everybody.
Please subscribe to our channel and click the "Good" button.
Thank you.
Is this it?
I think it's here. I think it's here.
I think it's here.
Bye-bye.
Next preview